yourjobspace.com 2012-11-14

# Your Job Space

###  109 Borough High Street,

###  London Bridge,

###  SE1 1NL

####  **Email:** privacy@YourJobSpace.com

By entering this site, you consent to the use of your personal information as set forth below.   
You can read our Privacy Policy below to see what information we collect and our security assurance.   
This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected by your job space   
this policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Your Job Space does not own or control or to people that Your Job Space does not employ or manage.   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Your Job Space™ website at www.Your Job Space ("Website"). On some pages, you can register for an account, make requests, and register to receive information. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include: 

  * Name 
  * State of Residence 
  * Zip Code 
  * Gender 
  * Email address 
  * Month and Year of Birth 
  * City 
  * Contact number 

##  Your Job Space uses information for five general purposes: 

  * To customize the advertising and content you see, 
  * To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, 
  * To contact you about specials and new products, 
  * To maintain and manage the distributor genealogy, and 
  * To allow other distributors to manage their businesses.

##  Security: 

Whether you place an order or create a profile, we use industry-standard secure server software (SSL) that encrypts all information you input before it is sent to the server. In addition, the entire customer data collected is protected against unauthorized access. Account Numbers are encrypted and stored in our server for six months after orders are entered.  
No data transmission over the Internet will be 100% secure. While we take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Upon receiving your transmission, we make all reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. However, you are ultimately responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username, passwords and/or any account information.   
To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."  

##  Information Sharing: 

Your Job Space uses the information we collect solely for our business purposes. We do not sell or share personal information to third parties other than those third parties who provide services vital to our business and to other distributors. However, we may also provide aggregate information and statistics about our customers, sales and related site information to our third-party providers, but this information and statistics will include no personally identifying information. Please note that we may release information in good faith as is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or protect our rights. 

##  Cookies and Sessions: 

Cookies are essential "invisible" data files that act as an electronic messenger between your computer and our website. Internet browsers have a notification option to let you know when an "invisible" cookie is being sent to you. Through your browser options you can choose not to accept the cookie. However, in not accepting the cookie, you may not be able to experience all functions of Your Job Space. 

##  Online Privacy Policy Only: 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

##  Links:

Our Site contains links to other Social sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information from them. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. 

##  Your Consent:

By using our website, you agree to let us collect and use information per the terms of this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. 

##  How Can You Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing your Your Job Space Profile. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

##  Making Changes to Your Personally-Identifiable Information:

You may update your personal information as necessary by logging into the Account Management section of Your Job Space’s back-office. Within Your Job Space’s back-office, you have access to your account information and have the ability to edit your information. In addition, you may contact us at info@Your Job Space.com to update your profile..
